McKelvey, Jean T. Papers /3001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- M (Box 48)
  - Monroe County 1 of 2 1968 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Monroe County 1968 2 of 2 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Monroe, County of - 1976 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Monroe County Sheriff's Dept. 1979 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Monroe County of 1980 1 of 2 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Monroe, County of 1980 2 of 2 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Monroe, County of 1982 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Monroe Co. Sheriff's Dept., 1985 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - MPR Construction Corp. 1972 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Muench-Kreuzer Candle Company, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 28)
- Na - NYC (Box 49)
  - National Airlines - 1976 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - National Cashet Company Inc. - 1957 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Nestle Co. 1 of 4, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Nestle Co. 2 of 4, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Nestle Co. 3 of 4, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Nestle Co. 4 of 4, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - New England Telephone and Telegraph Company 1 of 3, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - New England Telephone and Telegraph Company 2 of 3, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - New England Telephone and Telegraph Company 3 of 3, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - New England Telephone, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - New England Tele. Co. 1130-0146-85, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - New England Tele Co. 1130-2113-86, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - New England Telephone 1130-2417-86, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - New York, City University of - 1974 1 of 3 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - New York, City Univ. of - 1974 2 of 3 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - New York, City Univ. of - 1974 3 of 3 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- NYC BHE files 1-15 (Box 50)
  - NYC Board of Higher Education - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - NYC Bd. Of High Education - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - NYC Bd. Of High Education - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- NYC BHE files 16-23 (Box 51)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 16 of 46 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 17 of 46 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 18 of 46 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 19 of 46 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 20 of 46 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 21 of 46 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 22 of 46 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 23 of 46 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 24 of 46 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- NYC BHE files 24-31 (Box 52)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 24 of 46 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 25of 46 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 26 of 46 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 27 of 46 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 28 of 46 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 29 of 46 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 30 of 46 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 31 of 46 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- NYC BHE files 32-46 (Box 53)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 32 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 33 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 34 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 35 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 36 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 37 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - NYC BHE - 1973 38 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - NYC-BHE-1973 39 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - NYC-BHE-1973 40 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - NYC-BHE-1973 41 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - NYC-BHE-1973 42 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - NYC-BHE-1973 43 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - NYC-BHE-1973 44 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - NYC-BHE-1973 45 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - NYC-BHE-1973 46 of 46 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- NYS Department of Corr. - NYSEG (Box 54)
  - NY State Dept. of Audit and Central, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - N.Y. State Dept. of Correctional Services - 1975 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - N.Y. State Dept. of Correctional Services - 1976 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - 1 of 3 NYS Dept/ of Correctional Services (Simon), 1976 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - 2 of 3 NYS Dept. of Correctional Services (Simon), 1975 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - 3 of 3 NYS Dept. of Correctional Services (Simon), 1975 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - NY State Dept. of Correctional Services - 1983 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - 2 of 2 1983 NY State Dept of Correctional Services (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - N.Y. State Dept. of Correctional Services - 1984 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - New York State Dept. of Correctional Services - 1985 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - NY State Dept. of Correctional Services 1985-87, 1985-1987 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - New York State Dept. of Correctional Services - 1987 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - NYS Dept. of N.Y. Services (Orleans) '87, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - New York, Dept. of Correctional Services - 1987 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - New York Dept. of Correctional Services - 1987 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - N.Y. State Dept. of Correctional Services - 1988 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - N.Y. State Dept. of Labor - 1975 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - N.Y. State Dept. of Mental Hygiene - 1975 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - N.Y. State Dept. of Mental Hygiene - 1975 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - New York Dept. of Mental Hygiene - 1976 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - N.Y. State Dept. of Mental Hygiene - 1976 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - NYS Dept. of Mental Hygiene (Swim), 1975-1977 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - NYS Dept. of Mental Hygiene (Bailor) '77, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - New York State Dept. of Mental Retardation and Developmental Disabilities, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - NY State Dept. of Taxation + Finance - 1976 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - NYS Dept. of Transportation (O'Brien), 1981 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - New York State Division for Youth - 1983 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - NYS Drug Abuse Central Comm. (Church) 1 of 2, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - NYS Drug Abuse Central Comm. 2 of 2 Comm., 1971-1974 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - NY State Drug Abuse Central Commission - 1976 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - NYSEA + SONYE - 1979 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - NYS Elec. + Gas ('74), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 32)
- NYSEG - Niagara Falls (Box 55)
  - NYS Elec. + Gas (Tokes) 1 of 4, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - NYS Elec + Gas (tokos) 2 of 4, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - NYS Elec + Gas (tokos) 3 of 4, 1958-1975 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - NYS Elec. + Gas (tokos) 4 of 4, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - NYSEG - 1977 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - NYS Elec. + GAS Corp. '86, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - NYSEG - 1987 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - NY State Office of Drug Abuse Services '70, 1975-1982 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - NYS Office of Drug Abuse - 1977 1 of 2 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - NYS Off of Drug Abuse - CSEA 1977 - 2 of 2 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - New York Office of Employee Relations - 1975 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - NYS Office of Employer Relations - 1976 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - NYS Office of Mental Health (Ring) 1 of 2, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - NYS Off. Of Mental Health (King) 2 of 2, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - NY State Office of Mental Health - 1983 1 of 2 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - New York State Office of Mental Health - 1983 2 0f 2 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - New York, State Office of Mental Health 1983 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - New York State United Teachers, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - NYSU, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - New York (State University of.) - 1973 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - NYS University at Geneseo (Case # 85-44-D), 1982-1985 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - New York Telephone Co. - 1983 1 of 2 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - New York Telephone Co. - 1983 2 of 2 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Niagara Falls Teachers '69, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Niagara Falls Teachers A-70-6, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Niagara Falls Board of Ed. - 1970 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Niagara Falls Teachers A-70-11, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 27)
- Niagara Frontier - Onadog (Box 56)
  - Niagara Frontier Transportation Authority - 1985 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Niagara Frontier Transportation Authority 2 of 2 - 1985 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Niagara Mohawk Power Corp. - 1980 1 of 2 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Niagara Mohawk Power Corp. - 1980 2 of 2 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Niagara Mohawk Power Co. - 1983 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Niagara Univ. - 1983 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Niagara - Wheatfield CSD - 1978 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Northport - E. Northport 1 of 3, 1972-1977 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Northport - E. Northport 2 of 3, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Northport - E. Northport 3 of 3, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - North Tonawanda - 1971 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Nunda CSB of Ed. - 1968 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - NYNEX, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - O'Connor Chevrolet 1 of 2 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - O'Connor Chevrolet 2 of 2, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Olean Unity CSD, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Olean CSD 1 of 2, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Olean CSD 2 of 2, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Olin Corp., 1976 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Onondaga Community College 1 of 2, 1979-1980 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Onondaga Community College 2 of 2, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Onondaga Co. - Arguinzoni, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Onondaga, 1980-1982 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Onondaga Co. 1 of 2 Delany, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Onondaga Co. 2 of 2 Delany, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Onondaga Co. - Putzer 1 of 2, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Onondaga Co. - Putzer 2 of 2, 1982-1984 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Onondaga Co. - Adsitt, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 28)
- Or - Pa (Box 57)
  - Orchard Park CSD 1 of 2, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Orchard Park CSD 2 of 2, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Pan American - Fenton - 1 of 3 1973 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Pan American - Fenton - 1973 2 of 3 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Pan American - Fenton - 1973 3 of 3 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Pan american (Benoit) 1 of 3, 1976-1977 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Pan American (Benoit) 2 of 3, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Pan American (Benoit) 3 of 3, 1969-1975 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Pan Am. (Brooks) 1 of 6, 1977-1978 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Pan AM (Brooks) 2 of 6, 1974-1975 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Pan AM (Brooks) 3 of 6, 1977-1980 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Pan AM (Brooks) 4 of 6, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Pan AM (Brooks) 5 of 6, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Pan AM (Brooks) 6 of 6, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Pan American (Raahauge) 1 of 3 1980 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Pan American (Raahauge) 2 of 3 1980 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Pan American (Raahauge) 3 of 3 1980 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Pan American (Perez) 1 of 3, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Pan American (Perez) 2 of 3 1980 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Pan American (Perez) 1 of 3 1980 (Box 57, Folder 20)
- Pa - Roch. (1982) (Box 58)
  - Pan American (Sorenson) 1987 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Pan Am. (Clasm) 1 of 4 '88, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Pan Am. (Clasm) 2 of 4, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Pan Am. (Clasm) 3 of 4, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Pan Am. (Clasm) 4 of 4, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Pan. Am., 1981-1987 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania, Commonwealth of -, 1971-1977 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania State Colleges 1 of 3, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania State Colleges 2 of 3, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania State Colleges 3 of 3, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Pettibune Corp., 1976 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Pioneer CSD 1 of 2, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Pioneer CSD 2 of 2, 1974-1975 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Pioneer Central School, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Po Hlman Foundry, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Port Authority of Alleghany Co. 1 of 2, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Port Authority of Alleghany Co. 2 of 2, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Qualtop Beverages, 1957 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Riverside Book Cindery Inc., 1962 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Rochester, City of '70, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Rochester, City of '70, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Rochester, City of '74, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Rochester, City of 75-137, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Rochester, City of '76, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Rochester 1977 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Rochester, City of '77, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Rochester, 1977-1978 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Rochester, City of '78, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Rochester, City of 6/82, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 29)
- Roch. (City of, 1982) - Roch. CS (Box 59)
  - Rochester, City of 7/82, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Rochester, City of, 1982-1983 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Rochester, City of, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Rochester, City of, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - 1 of 2 Rochester, City of, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - 2 of 2 Rochester, City of, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Rochester, City of, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Rochester, City of, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Rochester, City of, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - '64 Rochester CSD 1 of 2, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - '64 Rochester CSD 2 of 2, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - '67 Rochester CSD, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - '67 Rochester CSD, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Bente Rochester, CSD, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Rochester CSD, Ad bloc Committee 1 of 6, 1966-1967 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Rochester CSD, 1968 Budget Impasse 2 of 6 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Rochester CSD, 1968 Budget Impasse 3 of 6 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Rochester CSD, 1968 Budget Impasse 4 of 6 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Rochester CSD, 1968 Budget Impasse 5 of 6 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Rochester, CSD 1968 Budget Impasse 6 of 6 (Box 59, Folder 20)
- Roch. CSD - Sh (Box 60)
  - Rochester CSD, 1967 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Rochester, CSD, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Rochester, CSD, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Rochester, CSD 1 of 2 1987 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Rochester CSD 2 of 2 1987 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Rochester Electrotype -and- Engraving Co., 1956 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Rochester Transit Corp., 1957 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Rochester Transit Corp., 1967 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Rok's Men Shop, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Rome Grader Corp., 1953 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Rush-Henrietta CSD, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Rush-Henrietta CSD, 1976-1977 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Rush-Henrietta CSD, 1981-1984 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Rush-Henrietta, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Rust Craft Broadcasting Company, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Schenectady CSD, 1950-1980 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Schoeller --, 1972-1974 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Schuler Foods '59, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Scott Aviation 1 of 2, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Scott Aviation 2 of 2, 1977 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Seneca, Co. of, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Seneca Falls Machine Co. 1 of 2, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Seneca Falls Machine Co. 2 of 2, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Shoe Farm Co., 1957 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Shuron '62, 1962 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Shuron '63, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Shuron '65, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 27)
- Sol - Syr (Box 61)
  - Solvay '53, 1953 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Solvay '54, 1954 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Solvay '57, 1957 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - South Colonie 1 of 3, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - South Colonie 2 of 3, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - South Colonie 3 of 3, 1976-1979 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Spaulding Composites Co., 1988 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Spaulding Fibre Co. #475, 1966-1967 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Spaulding Fibre Co. 1 of 2 #6332, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Spaulding Fibre Co. 2 of 2 #6332, 1956-1959 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Special Metals 1 of 2, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Special Metals 2 of 2, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Standard Rochester Brewing, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Sterling Drug Co., 1980 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Sterling Optical 1 of 2, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Sterling Optical 2 of 2, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Sterilon, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - St. Regis Paper Co., 1964 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Strippit/Di-Acro, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Stromberg-Carlson Corp., 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Sylvania 1 of 2, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Sylvania 2 of 2, 1958-1962 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Syracuse, City of, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Syracuse, City PBA 1 of 3, 1980-1983 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Syracuse, City PBA 2 of 3, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Syracuse, City PBA 3 of 3, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Syracuse, City Sch. Dist. 1 of 2, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Syracuse, City Sch. Dist. 2 of 2, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Syracuse Univ. '70, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Syracuse Univ. '71, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 30)
- Ta - Tr (Box 62)
  - Aiv Portugal, 1982 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Texaco 1 of 3, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Texaco 2 of 3, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Texaco 3 of 3, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Texas International Airlines, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Tobin Packing Co. '53, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Tobin Packing Co. '54, 1954 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Tobin Parking '58, 1958 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Tobin Parking Co. '60, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Trans continent Television Corp. 1 of 2, 1958-1960 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Trans continent Television Corp. 2 of 2, 1958-1960 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Trans International Airlines (Moreau) 1 of 4, 1976-1978 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Trans International Airlines (Moreau) 2 of 4, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Trans International Airlines (Moreau) 3 of 4, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Trans International Airlines (Moreau) 4 of 4, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Trans World Airlines (Granger), 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Trans World Airlines (Shields) 1 of 3, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Trans World Airlines (Shields) 2 of 3, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Trans World Airlines (Shields) 3 of 3, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Trans World Airlines (Rogers), 1977 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Trans World Airline (Crewdson) '84, 1984 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Trans World Airlines (Weaver) 1 of 3 '78, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Trans World Airlines (Weaver) 2 of 3, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Trans World Airlines (Weaver) 3 of 3, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Trans World Airlines (Elliston) 1 of 2 '80, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Trans World Airlines (Elliston) 2 of 2, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Trans World Airlines (Braithwaite) 1 of 3, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Trans World Airline (Braithwaite) 2 of 3, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Trans World Airlines (Braithwaite) 3 of 3 (Box 62, Folder 29)
- Tr - UA (1969-1970) (Box 63)
  - Trans World (Todd) '83, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Trans World Airlines 1985 (Todd) (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Trans World Airlines (Mitchell) 1 of 2 '86, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Trans World airlines (Mitchell) 2 of 2, 1969-1985 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Trans World Airlines - (Georgian) '88, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - True Temper 1 of 2, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - True Temper 2 of 2, 1978-1981 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Two Seventy Seven Ave. Restaurant, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - United Air Lines Kincheloe, Susan 12/20/67, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - United Airlines Kincheloe, Susan 12/20/67, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - United Airlines Kincheloe Susan 12/20/67, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - United Airlines Kincheloe, Susan 12/20/67 4 of 4, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - United Airlines 1968 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - United Airlines ALPA+SS 1968 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - United Airlines ALPA + SS 1968 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - United Airlines Kincheloe - 1968 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - United Airlines Dalton - 1909 1 of 4 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - United Airlines Dalton - 1969 2 of 4 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - United Airlines Dalton - 1969 3 of 4 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - United Airlines - Dalton - 1969 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - United Airlines Dalton - 1969 Xtra Copies (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - United Airlines Dalton - 1969 2 of 6 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - United Airlines Dalton - 1969 3 of 6 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - United Airlines Dalton - 1969 4 of 6 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - United Airlines Dalton - 1969 5 of 6 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - United Airlines Dalton - 1969 6 of 6 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - United Airlines - 1969 (Stiner + Richardson) (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - United Airlines, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - United Airlines 1969 (Stiner + Richardson) (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - United Airlines - 1969 (Searle)196 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - United Airlines Hamill - 1970 - Hearing 1 of 2 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - United Airlines Hamill - 1970 - Hearing 2 of 2 (Box 63, Folder 32)
- UA (1970-1972) (Box 64)
  - United Air Lines Hamill - 1970 - Hearings 1 of 4 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - United Air Lines Hamill - 1970 - Hearings 2 of 4 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - United Air Lines Hamill - 1970 - Hearing 3 of 4 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - United Airlines Hamill - 1970 - Hearings 4 of 4 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - United Airlines Morgan - 1970 1 of 4 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - United Air Lines Morgan - 1970 2 of 4 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - United Airlines Morgan - 1970 3 of 4 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - United Airlines - Morgan - 1970 4 of 4 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - United Airlines Morgan 1970 Hearings 1 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - United Airlines Morgan 1970 Hearings 2 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - United Airlines - Fitzsimmons - 1970 1 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - United Airlines Fitzsimmons - 1970 2 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - United Airlines Montoya - 1971 1 of 3 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - United Airlines Montoya - 1971 2 of 3 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - United Airlines 1 of 2 1971 (Ranzman) (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - United Airlines 1971 (Ranzman) 2 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - United Air Lines Elmslie - 1971 1 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - United Air Lines Elmslie - 1971 2 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - United Airlines (Roberts) - 1971 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - United Airlines Landsdale - 1971 - 1 of 3 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - United Airlines Landsdale - 1971 2 of 3 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - United Airlines Landsdale - 1971 3 of 3 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - United Airlines (Thomas) 1971 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - United Airlines 1972 (Olsen) (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - United Airlines 1972 (Olsen) 2 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- UA (1972-1973) (Box 65)
  - United Airlines Hauber - 1972 - 1 of 5 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - United Airlines Harbor - 1972 - 2 of 5 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - United Airlines Harbor - 1972 - 3 of 5 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - United Airlines Harbor - 1972 - 4 of 5 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - United Airlines Harbor - 1972 - 5 of 5 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - United Airlines Hauber - 1972 Extra Copies 1 of 3 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - United Airlines Hauber - 1972 Extra Copies 2 of 3 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - United Airlines Hauber - 1972 Extra Copies 3 of 3 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - United airlines Hauber - 1972 Transcript (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - UA Hauber - 1972 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - United Airlines Hauber - 1972 Transcript (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - United Airlines Hauber - 1972 Transcript (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - United Airlines Hauber - 1972 Transcript (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - United Airlines Hauber - 1972 Transcript (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - United Airlines - 1972 - Mueller (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - United Airlines - 1972 - Mueller (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - United Airlines - 1972 - Peterson (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - United Airlines - 1972 - (Rosenfeld, Anable) (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - United Airlines - 1972 = Ruech (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - United Airlines - 1972 - Ruech (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - United Airlines - Dalton - 1973 - 1 of 5 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - United Airlines - Dalton - 1973 2 of 5 (Box 65, Folder 22)
- UA (1973-1977) (Box 66)
  - United Airlines - 1973 - Dalton - 4 of 5 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - United Airlines - Dalton - 1973 3 of 5 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - United Airlines Dalton - 1973 5 of 5 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - United Airlines MEC 7-76 1 of 2, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - United Airlines MEC 7-76 2 of 2, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - United Flight ATND Lax. 16-76 Chi. 109-76 F 1 of 3 (Atkinson), 1976 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - United - Flight ATND - Lax 16-76, Chi. 109-76F (Atkinson) 2 of 3, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - United Flight ATND - Lax 16-76 Chi 106-76F 3 of 3 (Atkinson), 1976 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - United Airlines - 1976 (Box 66, Folder 9)